A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Organizational and Employment History, Accession 2018:041 FA743
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Organization Charts, 1990-2006; 1; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Organization Charts - Fiscal Year 2005 (2 folders), 2004 November-2005 May (Box 3, Folder 30-31)
    Organization; General Management; Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Management Services; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; China; Vietnam; Russia; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Grant Craft Program; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Information Processing Services; E-Content and Technical Services; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
  - Organization Charts - Fiscal Year 2006 (2 folders), 2005 November-2006 May (Box 3, Folder 32-33)
    Folder 32:) -- Organization; General Management; Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Management Services; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; China; Vietnam; Russia; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; International Initiative to Strengthen Philanthropy; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Grant Craft Program; Aids Work; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Information Processing Services; E-Content and Technical Services; Purchasing; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
    Folder 33:) -- General Management; Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Program Management; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; China; Vietnam; Russia; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; International Initiative to Strengthen Philanthropy; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Grant Craft Program; Aids Work; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Information Processing Services; E-Content and Technical Services; Office Servies; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration; General Management; Office of the President; Office of Communications; Program Division; Office of the Vice President -- Asset Building and Community Development; Community and Resource Development; Economic Development; Office of Program Management; India, Nepal, and Sri Lanka; Indonesia; China; Vietnam; Russia; Andean Region and the Southern Cone; Mexico and Central America; Brazil; Eastern and Southern Africa; Middle East and North Africa; South Africa and Namibia Program; West Africa; Office of the Vice President -- Knowledge, Creativity and Freedom; Education, Sexuality, and Religion; Media, Arts, and Culture; Peace and Social Justice Program; Governance and Civil Society Program; International Initiative to Strengthen Philanthropy; Human Rights; Special Initiative on Africa; Grant Craft Program; Aids Work; Office of the Secretary, Legal, Human Resources, Financial and Administrative Services; Internal Audit; Office of the General Counsel; Office of the Secretary; Grants Processing; Correspondence Control; Administrative Services - Office of the Director; Facilities Management; Information Technology; Global Infrastructure Services; Program Systems Development; Management Systems Development; Ford Foundation New York Infrastructure Services; Information Services; Research Services; Information Processing Services; E-Content and Technical Services; Office Services; Financial Services; Office of Human Resources; Investment Management Office of the Vice President; Fixed Income Investments; Private Equity; Equity Investments; Investment Administration
- Organization Charts - Information Services, 1970-2007; 2; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Organization Charts and Ford Foundation Structure Information, 1970-1978 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Organization Charts, 1980-2007 (Box 10, Folder 92-104, Box 11, Folder 105-119, Box 12, Folder 120-128)
- Staff Biographies and Directories, 1953-2008; 3; 1.9 Cubic Feet 5 letter document boxes
  - Biography Book Roster of Professional Staff (A-K), 1979 June (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Biography Book Roster of Professional Staff (L-Z), 1979 June (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Ford Foundation Office Procedures Guidelines, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    Sections include I. Introduction/Outline; II. Organization; III. "How To" Guide; IV. Secretarial Procedures; V. Style Guide (also includes Records Management and Telephone Techniques)
  - Ford Foundation Telephone Directory, 2008 January (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Ford Foundation Telephone Directory, 2008 July (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Ford Foundation Roster of Staff (A-L), 1981 May 1 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Ford Foundation Roster of Staff (M-Z), 1981 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Ford Foundation Agricultural and Resources Program Staff and Regular Consultants, 1978 July 1 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Ford Foundation Rosters of Staff, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Staff Bios - "A", 1958-2005 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Abrams, Frank W.
    Abrams, Frank Whittemore
    Adams, Emily Vargas
    Adams, Frederick B., Jr.
    Adams, Henry P.
    Adams, Richard N.
    Adebonojo, Enitan
    Aguerrebere, Joseph A., Jr.
    Aguirre, Mariano
    Akmajian, Herant
    Albert, Judith D.
    Albrecht, Herbert R.
    Allen, Frederick
    Allworth, Edward A.
    Alvarez, Sonia
    Alzmann, Germaine L.
    Amadei, Jennie M.
    Amaya, Abel C.
    Ambler, John S.
    Ames, Edward A.
    Amu, Ngozi
    Anderson, Anthony B.
    Anderson, David
    Anderson, Jerome W.
    Anderson, Kristin P.
    Anderson, Norma M.
    Anderson, Robert Bernard
    Anderson, Sonya L.
    Anderson, Valerie J.
    Andrade, C. Preston, Jr.
    Androvette, Robert A.
    Anglin, Roland V.
    Angulo, Carlos M.
    Anthony, Carl
    Antlov, Hans
    Armsey, James William
    Arnold, David D.
    Arnold, Edwin G.
    Arrington, Clarence
    Ashabranner, Brent K.
    Ashley, Walter Edward
    Atkin, Lucille C.
    Atkinson, Linda E.
    Atterbury, Boudinot P.
    Atwater, Verne S.
    Azzam, Fateh S.
  - Staff Bios - "B", 1955-2006 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    Back, Aaron I. Bader, William B. Baer, Werner
    Bailey, Charles R. Baker, Elizabeth Balan, Jorge Balwin, Charles Stephen Baldwin, Meagan Ball, Jeanette C. Ballard, Helen B. Banks, Robert B. Barber, Elinor G.
    Barker, Robert R. Barone, Carl Barry, Bruce S. Barry, Frank J.
    Barsalou, Judy Bartley, Mary-Hart Barzelatto, Jose Bassow, Whitman
    Batliwala, Srilatha Batten, David C. Bausch, James Bayard, Thomas Bechtel, Stephen Beckham, Edgar
    Beckman, George M. Beil, Dolf Belbase, Narayan Bell, David E. Becker, S. Jane Bell, Peter D. Benedict, Peter Bennett, Nicholas Benoit, Charles E.
    Benson, George M. Bentley, John, III Bentley, Ray Bentley, William
    Berelson, Bernard
    Berens, Rodney Bergin, Robert P. Bergman, Elihu Bergquist, Jean Berlin, Gordon
    Berresford, Susan V. Berrien, Jacqueline
    Berry, R. Albert
    Bertoletti, Robert G. Beserra, Leo L. Biddle, Sheila
    Bieber, Marion Bigalke, Terance W. Biggs, Tyler S.
    Biggs, William R. Bischoff, Irma E. Bissell, Richard Black, Eugene
    Black, James B. Black, Margaret A. Blair, Calvin P. Blelloch, David Basil Bloom, Clark C. Blumgart, John D. Boggs, Nancy H. Bohen, Frederick Martin Bohrson, Ralph G. Boland, Mary K. Bonbright, David Bonilla, Frank Booker, Queen Esther Boone, Richard W. Booz, Paul E.
    Borgmann, Carl W. Boring, Ron D. Bork, Timothy J. Botero, Rodrigo Bourne, Rosemary E. Boutwell, Mary Louise Bowles, Frank Boyce, Mary Alice Boynton, Thomas Whitney Bracken, Kieran M. Braswell, Robert B.
    Braun, Garwood A.
    Bresnan, Jack
    Brezenoff, Stanley Brimmer, Andrew Broehl, Wayne
    Bronzi, Piero Brooke, Nigel Brossier, Jacques Brothers, Dwight Brough, Owen, Jr.
    Brower, Brock
    Brower, John C.
    Brown, Charles Brown, Dorris Brown, Dyke Brown, Ellen Brown, Jerry Brown, Kimberli Brown, Prudence Brown, Stuart Brownlee, James F. Bruce, John Brucker, Mary E.
    Bruton, Henry J.
    Bryant, James W. Buchanan, Constance Hall Lewis, Elizabeth Buckley
    Bundy, McGeorge Bunker, Samuel Bunnell, Robert A. Burbridge, Peter R. Burke, Yvonne B.
    Burness, Carl Burnet, Robert Burnett, Penney Burns, Rose Ann Burris, Mary Ann Bush, Evelyn C. Lowe, Margaret B.
    Bushey, Bruce L. Butterfield, Victor L.
  - Staff Bios - "C", 1955-2008 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Cajka, Frank R. Jr.
    Caldiero, Marie
    Caldwell, Paulette M.
    Caliguire, Daria B.
    Campbell, Elizabeth C.
    Camper-Titsingh, Mary
    Cantwell, Lawrence
    Capistrano, A. Doris
    Capozzi, Elsie I.
    Carlisle, Carol
    Carlson, Bruce D.
    Carlson,, David Bertil Jr.
    Carlson, Reynold E.
    Carmichael, Bill
    Carol, Joy
    Carrillo, Joseph
    Carroll, Edward F.
    Carroll, Joan C.
    Carroll, Thomas H.
    Carter, Richard
    Cartter, Allan Murray
    Cartier, William J.
    Carucci, Albert A.
    Case, Harry Lawrence
    Case, Harry
    Catalano, Richard Michael
    Chafkin, Sol
    Challenor, Herschelle S.
    Chamberlain, Mariam K.
    Chamberlain, Neil W.
    Chambers, Robert J.
    Chandler, Robert W.
    Chandler, Robert Woodward
    Chang, Phyllis L.
    Chano, Junko
    Chanter, Cheryl N.
    Chavis, Kanawha Z.
    Cheit, Earl F.
    Chen, Lincoln C.
    Chien, Deborah H.
    Childs, Charles W.
    Choa, Andrew
    Chowdhry, Kamla
    Cicek, Selmin
    Clark, Paul
    Cleaves, Peter S.
    Clemente, Lilia C.
    Colautti, Aldo
    Cole, Fred
    Coleman, Elizabeth
    Coleman, Faith
    Coleman, John R.
    Cole, Barbette D.
    Collins, Norman R.
    Conroy, Michael E.
    Conway, Gordon R.
    Cook, Samuel DuBois
    Cool, John C.
    Coolen, Marion A.
    Cook, Sarah
    Coombs, Philip H.
    Cooney, Thomas E., Jr.
    Corrigan, Patrick A.
    Cotter, William R.
    Cottingham, Clement
    Counts, Gayle M.
    Coward, E. Walter, Jr.
    Cowles, John
    Cox, Larry R.
    Craigie, Marilyn S.
    Craigie, Marilyn
    Croley, Hugh T.
    Crossland, Fred E.
    Crouch, Christopher
    Crout, Viera
    Culbertson, Robert E.
    Cullen, Matthew J., Jr.
    Cummings, Hans
    Cummings, Ralph W.
    Cummings, William K.
    Cuninggim, Merrimon
    Cunningham, Bruce E.
    Curley, James R.
    Curvin, Robert
    Cutler, Thomas
    Cyr, Arthur I.
    Da Costa, Carmen D.
    Dado, Celeste
    Daly-Diep, Mairead
    Dassin, Joan R.
    Dawson, Victoria A.
    Duncan, Cynthia Mil
  - Staff Bios - "D", 1962-2004 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    Edward Francis D'Arms
    Carmen D. Da Costa
    Matthew Dagg
    Norman C. Dahl
    Henry P. Dart
    Maja D. Daruwala
    Michele S. Dash
    Joan R. Dassin
    Donald Kirk David
    Philip Davidson
    Fred Davie, Jr.
    Humphrey T. Davies
    William Edmund Davies
    Chester Davis
    Christopher L. Davis
    David M. Davis
    Gerald W. Dean
    Danilo D. Decena
    Peter E. de Janosi
    Joecelyn DeJong
    Guillaume de Spoelberch
    Jorge Deju
    Keiko I. DeLille
    Nancy W. Dennis
    Carl W. Desch
    Cecile C. DeSweemer
    Diane L. DeVito
    John J. Dickinson
    William R. Dimmler
    Laketch Dirasse
    John A. Dixon
    R. Harcourt Dodds
    William Donaldson
    Hedley Donovan
    John P. Doran
    Howard Dressner
    Robert Drysdale
    William Duggan
    Richard Dunlap
    Jane Dunne
    Mallika Dutt
    William M. Dyal, Jr.
  - Staff Bios - "E", 1954-2007 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    Eastman, Nicholson J.
    Ebersole, Mark C.
    Eddison, John C.
    Eddy, Junius
    Edens, David
    Edley, C. F.
    Edwards, Robert H.
    Edwards, Wesley S.
    Egger, Rowland
    Eguizabel, Cristina
    Ehle, John
    Ekstrom, Alfred J.
    El Husseiny, Basma El
    Elliott, Carolyn M.
    Elliott, Howard J. C.
    Ellis, James R.
    Emig, Otto Robert
    English, John W.
    Ensminger, Douglas
    Epstein, Simon R.
    Erf,, Herbert A., Jr.
    Esola, Ronald
    Esquivel, Angela
    Esser,, George, Jr.
    Ethridge, Mark F.
    Eurich, Alvin C.
    Evans, Kirk
    Everton, John Scott
  - Staff Bios - "F", 1953-2006 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    Falconer, Alsie J.
    Fallon, Dennis D.
    Fantini, Mario R.
    Farrell, James C.
    Farrell, John
    Faulhaber, Ingrid
    Faurot, Allen H.
    Faust, Clarence
    Fay, Chip
    Feder, Arlene V.
    Federici, James A.
    Fehnel, Richard H.
    Feinberg, Paul J.
    Feinstein, Marvin Jack
    Feldman, Marvin Sims
    Feldstein, Hilary P.
    Feller, Nancy Edward
    Felling, William L.
    Fennell, Doriss J.
    Fenton, Patrick Douglas
    Ferguson, Alan
    Ferry, Ping F.
    Fienup, Darrell Richard
    Finberg, Donald J.
    Finkelstein, David Barry
    Firstenberg, Paul Benjamin
    Fisher, H. Beth
    Fisher, Susan
    Fitch, James Butler
    Flora, Cornelia L.
    Flora, Jan Davis
    Floyd, Virginia
    Flynn, Jeremiah
    Foote, Richard
    Ford, Benson
    Ford, Henry L.
    Forman, Shepard K. E.
    Forsberg, Ingvar L.
    Fox, Arthur J.
    Fox, Melvin Peter
    Fraenkel, A.
    Franck, Jane
    Frank, Arlene
    Franz, Sharon
    Fredericks, Wayne
    Fredericks, J. E.
    Freeman, Howard
    Freilich, Sanford
    Freymann, Moye
    Friendly, Fred
    Frodin, Reuben W.
    Fry, Gerald R.
    Fuchs, Victor P.
    Fuller, William H.
    Funari, John
  - Staff Bios - "G", 1955-2000 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    Gaberman, Barry
    Gabriel, Nicholas
    Gaer, Felice D.
    Gaither,, Horace Rowan Jr.
    Gabriel, Myriam A.
    Gall, Allan Robert
    Galligan, Donald J.
    Galloway, Diane L.
    Gamble, Ruth S.
    Gamble, William Keith
    Gant, George F.
    Garceau, Oliver
    Gardner, James A.
    Garling, Marguerite L.
    Garrison, Lloyd M.
    Garsoian, Nina G.
    Garvin, Ann E.
    Gary, Ian Patrick
    Gault, Ronald T.
    Geithner, Peter
    George, Bryant
    George, Terrence R.
    Gerhart, John
    Germain, Adrienne
    Gerson, Cynthia
    Giamatti, A. Bartlett
    Gibb, Bruce Lorenzo
    Gibbs, Christopher J. N.
    Gilbert, Elon H.
    Giles, Walter K.
    Gilmore, Sandra
    Gladieux, Bernard L.
    Goddard, James L.
    Goldmann, Robert B.
    Goldrich, Daniel
    Goldsen, Rose K.
    Goldstein, Lawrence H.
    Gonzales, Adrian
    Goodman, David E.
    Goodman, Jane
    Goodwillie, Susan R.
    Goodwin, Craufurd David
    Trottenberg, Arthur D.
    Goodyear, Richard
    Gordon, Kermit
    Stratton, Julius
    Gordon, Lorraine R.
    Gordon, R. A.
    Gordon, Sheila C.
    Gordon, Stanley Thomas
    Gormbley, Bill
    Gottlieb, Leslie
    Gould, Lawrence McKinley
    Graham, George A.
    Graham, Lucile
    Granger, John E.
    Grant, David H.
    Greaves, Peggy H.
    Green, Carl J.
    Greene, Robert Paul
    Greenleaf, William
    Gregory, Stanley W.
    Griffiths, G. H.
    Grinker, William J.
    Gross, Grudzinska
    Guevara, Milwida
    Gulick, Luther
    Gustafson, Harold C.
    Gwatkin, Davidson R.
  - Staff Bios - "H", 1955-2002 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    Haas, Walter A. Jr.
    Hadley, Disbrow
    Hagler, Jon L.
    Hahn, Philip M.
    Hakim, Peter
    Hall, A. Gridley
    Hall, Harvey Porter
    Hall, Katherine
    Halse, Michael
    Hamilton, Vernon
    Hanna, Judith B.
    Hanratty, Martin E.
    Hanson, Haldrore
    Harari, Maurice
    Harbison, Frederick
    Harbison, Ralph W.
    Hardin, Lowell S.
    Harding, Mary
    Hardy, Gladys Chang
    Hardy, Neal J.
    Harford, Maura
    Harik, Iliya F.
    Harkavy, Oscar
    Harkness, James S.
    Harrington, Fred H.
    Harris, Donald S.
    Harris, Michael S.
    Harris, James T. Jr.
    Harrison, Gordon
    Hartmann, Francis X.
    Hathaway, Dale E.
    Hatzfeldt-Donhoff, Hermann
    Hauser, Philip
    Havener, Robert D.
    Heald, Henry Townley
    Heaps, David
    Heard, George Alexander
    Heffner, Jane E.
    Heilman, Elizabeth G.
    Hempel, Margaret L.
    Henderson, John H.
    Henderson, Vivian W.
    Henry, William J.
    Herman, William A.
    Hernandez-Alvarez, Jose
    Herrey, Antony
    Hertel, Thomas
    Hertford, Reed
    Hertz, Willard
    Heussler, Robert
    Hiatt, Thomas A.
    Hilberry, Clarence B.
    Hill, Arthur H.
    Hill, Forrest F.
    Hill, Rey Marshall
    Hill, Rueben
    Hilliard, John F.
    Himes, James R.
    Hinchcliffe, Jane E. (Jane Mavity)
    Hind, Robert R.
    Hoberman, Anthony
    Hoffman, Paul
    Hofmann, Edward G. III
    Hogg, Charlotte C.
    Hogg, Sir Christopher
    Holiday, Herman Joe
    Hollander, Neil
    Holmes, Horace C.
    Holmes, James P.
    Hooker, Gertrude Stephenson
    Hopkins, Richard A.
    Horah, Gerald V.
    Horlick, Gary N.
    Horn, Marjorie C.
    Horovitz, Richard A.
    Howard, Craig
    Howard, John
    Howard, John Brigham
    Howe, Harold II
    Hudson, Kenneth
    Humphreys, John
    Hungate, Jess
    Hunter, David R.
    Hunter, Guy
    Hunter, Marsha
    Huntley, James Robert
    Hussein, Adel
    Hutchins, Robert M.
    Hyden, Goran
    Lewis, Elizabeth Buckley
    Lowe, Margaret B.
  - Staff Bios - "I", 1955-2002 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    Ihonvbere, Julius
    Ilchman, Warren F.
    Illich, Michael J.
    Iltis, Carolee E.
    Indorf, Hans
    Inghilterra, Marianne D.
    Irelan, William T.
    Iritani, Chika A.
    Isenberg, Arthur
    Ispahani, Mahnaz
    Iverson, Kenneth R.
    Ivy, James T.
  - Staff Bios - "J", 1955-2000 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    Jackanicz, Theodore M.
    Jacob, Renate M.
    Jaffe, Jen
    Jaffe, Sanford M.
    Jarvis, Lovell S.
    Jeffrey, Richard Raught
    Jiggins, Janice L. S.
    Johnson, A. A.
    Johnson, Anna
    Johnson, Clifford R.
    Johnson, Dorothy M.
    Johnson, William Bert
    Johnson, Howard C., Jr.
    Johnson, Sam H., III
    Johnstone, D. Bruce
    Jones, David B.
    Jones, Eldon L.
    Jones, Nikola K.
    Jones, Sidney R.
    Jordan, James R.
    Jordan, Vernon E., Jr.
    Joyce, Jean
    Jumper, Roy E.
  - Staff Bios - "K", 1953-2005 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    Kahane, Michele
    Kalarchian, Mardig
    Kale, Pratima
    Kangas, Lenni Williams
    Kanter, John F.
    Kaplan, Boris D.
    Kapp, Richard
    Katz, Milton
    Kavanagh, John J.
    Kavros, Harry E.
    Keady, Louise W.
    Kecskemety, Helen
    Keenan, Terrance
    Kellar, Hazel A.
    Kelly, Eamon M.
    Kelly, George H.
    Kelly, James A.
    Kelsey, Clyde E.
    Kemp, Philip A.
    Kennan, George F.
    Kennedy, John P.
    Kennedy, Roger G.
    Keogh, Kevin
    Kershaw, Joseph A.
    Kerwin, Robert W.
    Kessinger, Tom G.
    Kieloch, Edward A.
    Kiene, Werner
    Kiley, Dan
    Kimbler, Moselle
    Kingsley, John Donald
    Klein, Harold Alexander
    Knight, Peter T.
    Knipschild, Florence M.
    Knowles, Marjorie Fine
    Koch, Janet E.
    Koch, Sigmund
    Kocher, James E.
    Koenig, Michael A.
    Kohl, Wilfrid L.
    Konomos, Susan Dunn
    Koprowski, John J.
    Korbonski, Andrzej
    Koriath, Janet C.
    Korotzer, Lee
    Korten, David C.
    Korten, Frances F.
    Koslow, Jules
    Kosovec, John J.
    Kostyra, Maddaline A.
    Kranich, Elaine C.
    Krasevac, Kimberly
    Krasner, Gladys
    Krasno, Richard M.
    Krauss-Kelleher, Deborah
    Kriesel, Herbert C.
    Kubasik, Ben
    Kuder, Katherine
    Kuesel, Arnold J.
  - Staff Bios - "L", 1953-2003 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    Lacey, Richard A.
    LaHoud, John L.
    Lake, Laura
    Lambourne, Richard W.
    Land, Edward Herbert
    Langton, Kenneth P.
    Lapple, James H.
    Larrabee, Charlotte S.
    Larsen, Roy Edward
    Laskin, Paul L.
    Lauchner, Julian H.
    Lavelle, Virginia C.
    Lawrence, Cheryl N.
    Layton-Thomas, Hazel L.
    Lazarevic, Martha E.
    Lederer, Ivo J.
    Lee, Andre
    Lee, Andrew J.
    Leeds, Elizabeth R.
    Leggett, Brenda J.
    Leighton, Leonard
    Delong, Donald C.
    LeMelle, Wilbert J.
    Lenagh, Thomas H.
    Lenton, Roberto L.
    Leonard, Ann
    Lerner, Jerrold B.
    Lesch, Ann M.
    Levine, Aaron J.
    Lewis, Arthur
    Lewis, Ben W.
    Lewis, Keisha
    Lewis, Stephen R., Jr.
    Lieberman, Irving
    Lieberman, Seymour
    Light, Jay O.
    Lightfoot, William I.
    Lindsay, Franklin A.
    Lindsay, Jennifer M.
    Linkonis, Anthony W.
    Lipscomb, James Samuel
    Lipsky, Michael
    Lisniewski, Theresa H.
    List, Claire
    Little, George F. G.
    Livingston, William C. III
    Lobanov, Oleg
    Lockhart, Lawrence A.
    Lockwood, William W.
    Longley, Clifford B.
    Lopez, Frank
    Lopez, Jose G. Jr.
    Lopez, Joseph R. Jr.
    Loudon, John
    Loudon, Jonkkeer John Hugo
    Lowe, Margaret
    Lowenthal, Abraham F.
    Lowry, W. McNeil
    Loysch, Carolyn
    Luban, Robert G.
    Lydecker, Josephine G.
    Lynch, Dennis O.
    Lynch, Roberta
    Lytle, Ronn K.
  - Staff Bios - "Mc", 1955-2002 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    MacEachron, David W.
    MacKusick, Meredith H.
    MacLeod, Norman W.
    McAuley, Mary J.
    McCarthy, Catherine A.
    McCarthy, Florence E.
    McCarthy, Nancy
    McCloy, John Jay
    McClymont, Mary E.
    McCue, Frank William
    McCusker, Henry F.
    McDaniel, Joseph M.